dealradar.com 2013-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Dealradar.com :: Local Offers | Restaurant Deals | Spa Deals | Local Deals | Deal-a-Day Sites

### Effective as of September 21, 2011

Dealradar.com is a reference guide that connects you with offers from local businesses in various cities. Local Offer Network, Inc. and Dealradar.com (collectively “we”) maintain Dealradar.com and all of its subdomains, syndication feeds and mobile versions referred to as “The Site” as a service to you our “users” for informational purposes only. Your access to or use of The Site means that you accept these Terms of Use and the terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy. 

Dealradar.com is committed to maintaining the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit Dealradar.com. 

##### 1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

**Information you give us:** We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our mailings or feeds, respond to a survey or fill out a form. As appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, living and work address. You may, however, visit our site without registering or providing these details.

**Information we gather from your use of our services and from 3rd Party Data partners:** We collect information about the offers and content you click on with our site, and if you end up purchasing those offers. This is both for business purposes and to allow us to understand how you are using our site.

Additionally, we work with third parties who use cookies and other technologies to gather and provide interest data that allows us to effectively personalize content on this site. We use the information collected in conjunction with information gathered through our website and information you provide voluntarily in order to provide you with a personalized experience. Our current partners who assist in the personalization of your experience are listed below. Please review each data provider`s privacy policy to learn more about their respective privacy practices, including opting-out from any information they gather.

  * eXelate
  * Rapleaf

If you prefer to NOT see personalized content that is relevant to you and your interests, please click here and follow the "What's This?" link to update your preferences. Please note that if you choose to opt-out, you are only opting-out of personalized content on this website, and only for the current computer and browser you are using. If you delete or turn off cookies, this option will be reset. 

##### 2\. WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 
  * To send periodic promotional emails and the daily aggregated deals email 

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the services requested. 

If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

##### 3\. HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. All supplied sensitive information is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

##### 4\. DO WE USE COOKIES?

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables Web sites or other online service providers to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better personalization, site experiences and features. 

##### 5\. DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

##### 6\. THIRD PARTY LINKS

We include content and offers for third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

##### 7\. CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

##### 8\. CHILDRENS ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

##### 9\. TERMS OF USE

Please also visit our Terms of Use section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website. 

##### 10\. YOUR CONSENT

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

##### 11\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

All privacy questions or comments should be sent directly to _[privacy@dealradar.com](mailto:privacy@dealradar.com)_

This privacy policy was last modified on July 21, 2012.
